{"message": "Successfully uploaded", "questions": [{"answer": 1, "question": "How many sentences are there in this paragraph?", "question_type": 1}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Adjective.", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["dr.", "ram", "good", "is"]}, {"explanation": "", "question": "In the following sentence identify Verb (3rd person singular present tense).", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 3, "options": ["good", "dr.", "ram", "is"]}, {"explanation": "ram is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is ram, Predeterminer in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "dr. is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Is dr., Pural Noun in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "good is Adjective", "question": "Is good, Adjective in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "is is Verb (3rd person singular present tense)", "question": "Is is, Verb (3rd person singular present tense) in the following sentence?", "comprehension": "dr. ram is good . ", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["True", "False"]}, {"explanation": "ram is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "dr. _____________ is good .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 2, "options": ["round", "khushboo", "ram", "capital"]}, {"explanation": "dr. is Singular or mass Noun", "question": "Select appropiate Singular or mass Noun from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": " _____________ ram is good .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 0, "options": ["dr.", "board", "head", "manan"]}, {"explanation": "good is Adjective", "question": "Select appropiate Adjective from the following to fill the black in the sentence.", "comprehension": "dr. ram is _____________ .", "question_type": 2, "answer": 1, "options": ["large", "good", "north-eastern", "civil"]}], "success": 1}